const literatureQuestions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "Who is the Nigerian author of the novel 'Things Fall Apart'?",
        answer: "Chinua Achebe"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the title of Chinua Achebe's second novel, published in 1964?",
        answer: "No Longer at Ease"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which Nigerian author won the Booker Prize for the novel 'The Famished Road'?",
        answer: "Ben Okri"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "In Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie's novel 'Half of a Yellow Sun,' which war is depicted?",
        answer: "Nigerian-Biafran War"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Who is the author of the novel 'Americanah'?",
        answer: "Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "In the novel 'To Kill a Mockingbird' by Harper Lee, what is the name of the lawyer defending Tom Robinson?",
        answer: "Atticus Finch "
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which novel by Jane Austen follows the life of the Dashwood sisters, Elinor and Marianne?",
        answer: "Sense and Sensibility"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Who is the author of the 'Harry Potter' book series?",
        answer: "Ben Okri"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which novel by F. Scott Fitzgerald is known for its portrayal of the Roaring Twenties and the character Jay Gatsby?",
        answer: "J.K Rowling"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is the title of George Orwell's dystopian novel published in 1949?",
        answer: "1984"
    },
]